visitstpeteclearwater.com 2018-10-08

# Privacy Policy | Visit St Petersburg Clearwater Florida

## I. About Visit St. Pete/Clearwater and Privacy

Visit St. Pete/Clearwater is the Official Tourism Marketing Organization for Pinellas County, Florida. It is a department of Pinellas County Government.

VisitStPeteClearwater.com is the official website of the Visit St. Pete/Clearwater.

Our postal address is:  
8200 Bryan Dairy Road,  
Suite 200  
Largo, FL 33777

We can be reached via e-mail at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#721b1c141d32241b011b062122315c111d1f).

### About Privacy

Your privacy is important to Visit St. Pete/Clearwater, and we will treat any of your information with care.

Our Privacy Statement lets you know how we handle personally identifiable information you share with us through our digital and printed communication vehicles.

## II. Privacy Statement ("Privacy Statement")

### Scope

This Privacy Statement explains how we collect and handle personally identifiable information you share with Visit St. Pete/Clearwater through our website, sweepstakes and promotional emails. It also describes our use of cookies and other tracking devices. It provides instruction regarding links to other websites, security of the information you provide and potential changes to the Privacy Statement. It provides contact information for questions and instructions for un-subscribing.

### Personal Information Collection

You may use our websites and other forms of internet-based communications to learn about Visit St. Pete/Clearwater products and services without disclosing any personal information beyond what you provided when requesting authorized Visit St. Pete/Clearwater publications, both digital or printed. We may ask you to provide us with personal information, for example, to access or use certain features or if you request additional information from Visit St. Pete/Clearwater and /or our Partners. Information that may be requested by Visit St. Pete/Clearwater includes: contact information, such as name, address, email address, and telephone number; demographic information, such as household information, age group, etc. and information about your travel interests.

### Personal Information Uses

Personal information that you voluntarily offer may be used to reply to your requests, to update and improve content on our website or to assist with marketing research. Such information includes but is not limited to survey responses, site registrations and information preferences, normally related to potential vacations in Pinellas County, Florida. This information is used to tailor communications to you, either by Visit St. Pete/Clearwater staff or by authorized Visit St. Pete/Clearwater communications entities.

Visit St. Pete/Clearwater will never sell your information. We will share your information ONLY with identified partners that are part of any sweepstakes or giveaway programs that are optional for users to enter for prizes and travel on our websites, such as VisitStPeteClearwater.com.

Personal information (name, address and phone number) may also be shared with Visit St. Pete/Clearwater contracted research firm, currently Research Data Services, Inc., for conversion study information as a result of requesting our Visitor Guide.

As a general rule, Visit St. Pete/Clearwater does not disclose any personally identifiable information collected online except where you have given us permission. We may disclose your personal information in conjunction with a government inquiry, or in litigation or dispute resolution, as required by [Florida Statute 119](http://www.leg.state.fl.us/statutes/index.cfm?app_mode=display_statute&url=ch0119/titl0119.htm&statuteyear=2000&title=-%3E2000-%3Echapter%20119). Information will only be disclosed if such information is not otherwise protected from disclosure by Statute.

### Cookies and Other Tracking Devices

We may use cookies and other tracking devices on our websites to allow us to measure site activity in aggregate, not on the individual level. This in turn allows us to provide a better user experience. Only information you voluntarily provide is stored in your customer file.

You can choose to refuse cookies — simply refer to your browser Help instructions to learn more about how to manage their use. If you wish to opt-out of cookies that allow us to monitor which advertising is most effective, [click here](http://dc.arrivalist.com/optout/).

### Links to Outside Websites

This site may contain links to third party sites not controlled by Visit St. Pete/Clearwater, which therefore are not covered by this privacy statement, such as those belonging to Visit St. Pete/Clearwater Partners and Sponsors. We recommend that you check the privacy statement of other sites you visit before providing any personal information.

### Security of Information

Visit St. Pete/Clearwater recognizes the importance of safeguarding personal information in our possession from theft, inappropriate use, or improper distribution. It should, however, be recognized that no company can perfectly protect personal information. Unauthorized attempts to upload or change information is strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Infrastructure Protection Act.

### Privacy Inquiries

If you have concerns or questions regarding Visit St. Pete/Clearwater's consumer privacy practices, please forward them to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#aefedcc7d8cfcdd7eef8c7ddc7dafdfeed80cdc1c3).

### Unsubscribe

You may unsubscribe to any St. Petersburg/Clearwater promotional email using the contact information listed above or through the unsubscribe link placed on all Visit St. Petersburg/Clearwater electronic newsletters.

### Changes to Privacy Statement

Visit St. Pete/Clearwater retains the right to change this Privacy Statement. For your benefit, we will post changes to this page in a timely manner.

### Hotel Reservations, Attraction Tickets & Vacation Deals

VisitStPeteClearwater.com provides the availability to transact and reserve hotel accommodations and attraction tickets through our websites. We use the third-party service Expedia that displays hotel and attraction information on VisitStPeteClearwater.com but manages any transactions directly through the property sites that users are passed onto. Any and all data provided through this process is used and maintained by the individual properties and attractions to facilitate delivery of the booking. Visit St. Pete/Clearwater does not manage or service any hotel or attraction transactions made through VisitStPeteClearwater.com and does not receive, or have access to, any credit card information submitted in the hotel transaction. Visit St. Pete/Clearwater makes no representation as to the accuracy or reliability of the offers being made, or of the values represented herein. Consumers wishing to take advantage of these offers are urged to use diligence in doing so and to understand that they do so at their own risk.
